[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
welcome to you all this is indrajit your
companion for today evening for this
live event I'm happy to note that there
are more than 100 branches that we have
that have joined us today for live
streaming along with the partners there
are the branches along with that we also
have people watching us live on YouTube
channel IELTS that we have created
exclusively for our partners so a very
momentous occasion for all of us as we
have come up with another product in our
health table which is not only Power
rich but they may have a lot of
potential to create a big market for us
we had launched Golden Shield a while
back and now with this new product
coming in we are strending our product
bouquet we have our Senior Management
with us today or to talk to you all as
we unveil a new product today so team uh
say thank you for joining us and thank
you partners for strengthening our
presence across we look forward to your
support as it continues and we continue
our journey for next phase of growth led
by the Health Products so on this
occasion moving ahead uh I would please
join your hands I would be welcoming Mr
aluk Agarwal executive director to
address you all uh over to you sir
welcome
sir you're on mute
all right
thank you in the chief and welcome you
all to this uh by event where we are
launching yet another product in this
case this is a body fight product rather
than the same product a completely new
product and I especially would like to
welcome
um all the partners who are there at
various locations who have been with us
in this health journey and also our own
employees who are present in the Nukem
corners of the country
so uh let me tell you that um I have
been part of the retail journey in the
last three months only and uh what I
have realized is that uh in the health
space uh we need a products which cater
to various types of needs we need people
for senior citizens we need people for
young people who are not married we we
want to be a product which has the
coverage for international travel so
there are various kinds of Deeds most of
those categories we had covered through
our various product sweets but whatever
gaps that we have been observing our
team in led by in the chief has been
coming up with new products we uh which
will cover up the gaps that when uh that
were open as far as product Suite is
concerned in this series Health
Advantage Plus is the newest product
which is the replacement of Health
Advantage and as you all know Health
Advantage as a product has one unique
feature that is our existing product on
the new product had one unique feature
that it had a Zone based pricing that
means places where the medical cost is
higher the pricing was different
compared to where the medical cost was
lower so we had categorized the entire
country into three zones and accordingly
we had priced this product across the
three zones but apart from this there
was
um other needs of various zones of
people one of the Prime needs of our
people was that we need international
coverage that people who can afford
uh a higher premium wanted to go
internationally for treatment of certain
diseases and that is what one of the
coverages that we have provided for this
Health Advantage Plus as a product
the other requirement was that the pre
and post hospitalization period
should be sufficiently wrong especially
for certain chronic diseases so uh in
this product we have now got 60 days
pre-hospitalization cover and 180 days
post hospitalization cover which is uh
which we think is a is a is a pretty
good uh time Gap in which people who
spend money pre-hospitalization and post
hospitalization shall be covered one of
our uh
Prime products uh that has been uh IL
take care the app that in which uh tele
and video consultation has become a real
Rich amongst people who have used this
in this Health Advantage Plus we have
given the benefit of unlimited
teleconsultations unlimited tele and
video consultations
so this will take care a um not only in
a lockdown like situation especially for
elderly and sick people who don't want
to move out repeatedly for their
consultations can do the preliminary
concentration through tele and video and
can follow it up with one physical
consultation if required so this will be
a Big Boon for those people especially
for those cities where uh where where
some Specialists are not available and
they can take a Telly and video
consultation from from a remote City and
then go on to the main city as and when
required uh one uh uh one one another
requirement that I had heard when I
traveled across the current tree is that
some day care procedures were covered as
far as our Health Advantage product was
concerned and some daycare uh procedures
were not covered in this product almost
all daycare procedures have been covered
so this these are the some of the few
features that I can immediately recall
and I wanted to tell you I but there are
some more features which are unique to
this product it has got a very high
summary insured of three crores if
somebody wants some insured of three
crores and more
they can add three crores up to three
crores they can Avail of this product so
um with uh with the launch of this
product I think one of the major gaps of
the industry will be filled up by this
uh product and it is up to us both our
employees as well as our partners who
are present in various cities across the
country to to Avail of this product and
increase our distribution progress
across the country so let us look
forward we look forward to a good amount
of traction coming for both you as well
as you individually as well as a week we
as a company it is a good traction and
let us serve the community to in the
best interests of everybody the all the
stakeholders we best served through this
product thank you
thank you so much sir it has really been
encouraging and I'm sure as we are the
partners and the teams also will be
equally excited and would be looking
forward to this product uh now uh say I
would want to invite Mr Amitabh Jan head
of underwriting and claims Health
product and uh he and his team has been
instrumental in getting this product to
you so over to Amitabh sir
thanks uh it's a real pleasure to
connect with all of you again and as we
promised the last time uh you know we'll
be here every two to three months to
give you one more product and we live to
that promise as per our theme of they
right that uh you know you will be
at least for product point of view you
will not be having any Darth of options
as far as you know I say hello mad in
their renewed uh bigger and energy for
health is concerned so you know uh I'm
very happy to introduce the product to
you already uh our executive director Mr
Adobe has already introduced some of the
features to you and uh spoken about it
uh as to how we are going about this I
wouldn't want to talk about every
feature because you know I'll be
stealing the Thunder of people who are
going to talk further and the
presentation that is going to be made I
just tell you the approach we've been
taking is that while we have been
working on various products we have what
we have done is that whatever we got
from our incoming company uh as products
uh some of the good features we have
maintained but we also realize that some
of our good features in our current
offerings of chi and other products were
missing so that is something that we
have plugged in and at the same time uh
with our continuous engagement with you
and all the other Market forces we
realize that there are certain features
that need to be added so those have been
added and the third part has been how do
we make it more Innovative so we have
introduced certain features which you
will see for example the vaccine
discount that we brought in that's very
very unique to the market
you'll hear more about it in the
presentation and when uh you know uh the
speakers ahead of me will talk to you
about it uh the whole idea is that we
offer something which is very very
comprehensive very very loaded in terms
of feature but yet at the same time
those are some of those are optional so
that you know it suits all pockets and
third we bring with each launch some
Innovation some new thing to the market
which is missing and that's the theme we
continue and that's what you will find
in this product uh another feature which
uh you know adopt sir talked about is
the whole approach that we've been
taking now is that we want to offer a
holistic 360 degree
a you know way of connecting with the
customer on health like we said we want
to be partners on their health and
therefore uh OPD is becoming an
important part of it
so the be fit product which you're
already selling will also be available
along with this product to be sold so
that you are able to offer not only you
know the teleconsultations and the
ambulance service that comes with it uh
but also the uh be fit comprehensive
offering on opt as a writer to this
product along with rest of the features
that you know that are coming to you
along with uh you know the new sort of
launch
uh the whole emphasis is that at every
stage our customers should be able to
take care of their health better be it
OPD be it Wellness uh be it early uh
diagnosis and hospitalization and Day
Care procedures of all types and
ensuring that as a follow-up if they
need more medication post follow-up you
know the post hospitalization expenses
are also covered and at the time of
renewal they get certain benefits for
example if they've taken a vaccine they
get certain discounts because they are
taking care of their health better so
those are the things that we have
thought about and though that's the uh
you know overall uh Focus to ensure that
not only you have great product great
features great pricing but also we
service our customers well so that they
are okay you know taking care of their
health better ultimately if our
customers remain healthy our portfolio
remains healthy and we are able to keep
our premiums in control so with uh with
that I would like to hand over to the
next uh speaker and wish you all the
best looking forward to great sale and
making this the number one product in
the market because now you've given it
the edge that it always had but now
we've given it the sheen you know the
edge in Head Health Advantage has become
much more sharper thank you
thank you so much amitab sir so it has
been a pleasure and uh said listening to
you say getting to know that more
products are there in pipeline I'm sure
Partners would be excited as well and
with bifid coming in that tire spectrum
of healthcare is covered uh of course
moving on I'll say the less welcome Mr
saroj as well head of health and krg or
to address you all welcome sir
yeah
thanks in the uh once again a very very
warm welcome to each of our partners and
our colleagues out there both attending
physically in our branches and digitally
um
also mentioned the same thing
and that effort was we said we will add
more people you have seen each of our
branches have multiplied they are now if
there was one person earlier there's
seven or eight people handling the
exclusive health business and across
lunches whether it's a smaller Plant Big
Branch we are seeing huge amount amount
of increase in our colleagues there to
service you better to talk to you so
that's a matter of Pride the second we
said will increase our network uh you
know today in terms of a cashews Network
both for opt which is Network
the event teasing and then we also said
that we will be number one in terms of
product and we are very happy we are
almost beating almost every 40 days last
very recently we had gathered and we had
launched uh the product golden sheet um
and that product is already ahead uh we
have started selling in good numbers
good policies have come in or they just
segments
and now we are very very happy to get
you another product uh I will again not
talk about the features while we believe
the international coverage is the most
Optimum feature in that product but that
I think will get covered what is more
important is uh you know today our
commitment which is getting shown by
launcher products people and Service
delivery that we are in this business
for long term and we are the strong
brand and you should you know you should
know that when we as a company come and
we are committed to that business we
will grow very fast and along with you
and we will ensure every segment of the
market is covered and that's what we are
doing so again again thank you so much
for coming and we are happy to present
you this product the only request is uh
listen to this we will be doing more
trainings over the next week one week
but I think as Amitabh said you know
there's an extra Edge in this product
with the new features launch but that
edge can only get sharpened and utilized
when you start selling it so to all our
partners and colleagues in this my
request is let's look at this product
and let's go whole lot and cover more
and more people and start selling this
product in big numbers thank you
with this I think we'll look at the new
launch AV overview
let the product be shown to the partners
now
then we have the evening please
[Music]
foreign
we are always on the moon
chasing goats realizing dreams
and discovering newer joys in life
what if you could have the protection of
a trusted Health partner every step of
your way forward
whether you're home or abroad present it
Asia Lombard Health Advantage Apex plus
plan a health partner that protects you
at home or abroad it has been designed
to deliver you worldwide coverage so you
can experience enhanced Peace of Mind
confidence and freedom
the bouquet of offerings in this plan
includes some insured limit up to three
crores 60 days free and 180 days post
hospitalization expenses Delhi
consultations coverage for all day care
treatments domestic air ambulance cover
home care cover starting with Worldwide
coverage for hospitalization you can get
protection for expenses up to the sum in
short
this benefit can be unlocked for a sum
insured of 25 lakhs and above
with the pre and post hospitalization
benefit you get covered for medical
expenses incurred for a period up to 60
days before and 180 days after an
insured person's admission to hospital
it also offers tele consultations and
recommendations for routine health
concerns by qualified medical
practitioner giving you more and prompt
access to Wellness
further on the ambulance cover feature
includes the expenses incurred on
emergency bases for using domestic air
ambulance services
the domestic air ambulance service
coverage is up to the summon short
medical expenses incured by in short for
daycare treatments as an inpatient in a
hospital for less than 24 hours are also
covered Home Care treatment expense is
also covered for a customer to opt to
get treated at the comfort of their
homes provided it is prescribed by the
doctor too apart from these enhanced
features the new Health Advantage plan
comes with a host of other benefits that
ensure robust coverage so give your
health care the advantage it deserves
with unciation Lombard Health Advantage
Apex plus black foreign
ERS I'm sure you would have found lot of
interesting features that you can talk
to your customers about and as far as
said we will look forward to see that
lot many policies now are getting sold
of this new plan coming in
uh we I would also want to appeal at
this stage that you should subscribe to
our YouTube channel called IL buzz and
you will get all the new updates about
health insurance all the developments
that we are doing on that itself so if
you have not subscribed it yet please do
subscribe it and also recommend to your
friends and family to subscribe to it
now I would hand over the stage to
Abhishek saraf for our underwriting
ahead for health and uh he would be
taking you through the product features
in details over to you Abhishek
thank you and once again very well warm
welcome to everyone who have joined this
live event of Health Advantage
so I think uh most of the new feature I
think
sir already said okay what new we have
introduced in this existing product but
still I want to basically uh highlight
all the features which are basically
inbuilt in the product
the customer to have an extra feature
with an additional premium so what
happens every every customer have the
different needs so we didn't want it to
complicate the product and create plans
this time so as you know we had prime
Apex and Royal so what we wanted we
wanted to introduce a single Plan called
Apex plus where we have all the sum
insured from 5 lakhs to three crores and
with all the features where customer can
choose and basically uh take as per
their needs so let's uh go to the
presentation and look what are the
features which are basically coming in
this new plan
FX Plus
yes can you move to next slide
so as you see
so there are two basically side of a
plan where one is an inbuilt covers and
the other is optional cover so if you
see orange line wherever we have
mentioned orange line that's the inbuilt
cover which comes inbuilt in the plant
with the basic premium
and wherever we have highlighted the
blue line which is the optional cover
like modernity CI flame protein SI
protector
So the plan is a good mix of both the
both the features which are inbuilt and
which are optional because modern DX
cipa we believe that not an all
individual requires such kind of a cover
that's the reason we have made that as
an option cover
now we come to the inbuilt covers one to
one the first one in patient
hospitalization as you all know the
measure the basic uh feature of the any
Indemnity product is the inpatient
hospitalization which means any
treatment any illness or any disease
which has been covered with 24 hours of
hospitalization hospitalization
apart from that we also covered
inpatient ions treatment so as if you
are aware okay in many of the products
the IU statement are covered basically
with a sub limit but the good thing
about this product is here we don't have
any capping so you can use inpatient IR
treatment up to some insured so in case
a person have opted for 10 lakh some
insured the person can utilize this
benefit are you statement up to 10 lakhs
the third benefit is some in short
restore so as you see in the product
where we also cover same illness
restoration so what do we mean by
seamless restoration so I will just give
you an example so in case the policy is
of 10 lakhs and in the first claim a
person has
a hard name of five lives so what
happens we pay five lakh and now the
balance is only five lakh what happens
in case a customer hospitalized second
time in a year
and what forbidden again the person is
claiming for a heart and there is a
claim amount of 10 lakhs so what happens
normal course of policy what happens we
just pay five lakhs because the balance
I'm in short is only five lakhs but what
good thing about this restore is that we
cover same illness up to some insured so
in this scenario where I have given
example the first claim of five lakh was
paid the balance was only five lakhs now
again that five lakh will be stored to
10 lakhs and this 10 lakh will be paid
to the customer so in total the customer
have claimed 15 lakhs for the same
illness
so this same illness is stored only once
in a year so in case a person has
claimed 10 plus 10 the feature will
cease to exist there
now coming to guaranteed cumulative
bonus so what we have seen uh Wherever
Whenever there is a claim basically we
reduce humidity bonus so but when we add
the word guaranteed Community bonus in
the product what does that mean this
mean hey basically whenever takes a
claim to a year it will give you 20 of
the submit shot as an additional sum in
short but in the event of claim we won't
deduct that some insert which was
already given to you during the clean
free here so every year a person can
accumulate 20 percent of the summon shot
maximum up to 100 percent
so there was a consonant feedback okay
basically uh the product where we where
we want the community bonus to be 100 in
some product that
amount was restricted to 50 so now in
Health Advantage basically you can earn
20 percent of the community bonus every
claim free year up to 100 percent
another unique feature about this
product is animal bite vaccination so
what happens in case of any animal bite
in case a four-legged animal or snake
what happens if you require any kind of
immunization or the vaccination after
the bite that is covered up to ten
thousand so even this is a very good
feature where uh I think unique in the
market where only few companies are
covering this uh vaccination
another most important thing the daycare
procedure which currently we were
covering only 586 digit procedure so as
the feedback came okay there shouldn't
be any restriction on the Decay
procedure and we also believe in that
and we remove that restriction of 586
daycare procedure and we made it all day
care procedure so now any day care
procedure which come under the
definition of care will be covered under
our product FX Plus
another big feature organ donor expense
so what we mean by organ donor light
span so in some cases what happens to
press scenario we have seen where the in
short require the organ from the Donate
and there's a lot of expense uh which
basically uh comes when the dhoni uh
give the organ to uh the insured on
harvesting uh the organ so whatever the
expense
maybe uh into the any limit what are the
sub in short we are covering up to some
insure so there will be no restriction
like 10 percent of the policy or fifty
thousand percent of the 50 000 uh of the
sub limit but here we are covering up to
some insured so a person who bought a
policy of 50 lakhs they don't have to
basically relope into any kind of
supplements so if the expense are up to
some insure will pay up to something
sure
domestic Road ambulance I think this uh
feature everybody is aware here we are
paying one percent of some insured
maximum to ten thousand uh uh per policy
here for every event so in case if there
is any multiple hospitalization we will
pay one person maximum 10 000 on each
and every hospitalization
another unique uh feature which I'm
covering is your biopric surgery so what
happened uh in case a custom in case the
insured BMI is more than 40 and they
have sometimes kind of come up with like
heart condition or a hypertensive or
type 2 diabetes then basically we are
providing that cover up to 50 of the sum
in short maximum to 10 lakhs so this is
additional Advantage uh which the
customer is getting where you will see
in certain scenario that this kind of
surgery are excluded but in our product
this is included with a sub limit of 50
of the sum insert
now sometimes what happens the
hospitalization days increases uh maybe
because of critical illness or maybe
because of prolonged illness so number
of uh length of oscillation goes beyond
10 days so what happens in that case so
we have one another benefit of
convalescence benefit so wherever there
is a length of stay which increases 10
like 10 days and above in
hospitalization we pay a lot of some
benefit of 20 000 so this expense might
be considered as all the other expenses
which are basically happens fairly uh
during the hospitalized and maybe the
conveyance or maybe other uh expense
which are not under policy that's the
reason we give some benefit of 20 000
per policy here
another unique thing the health Checker
so in previous I think the product you
have seen the health checkup account was
very restrictive in this product we are
covering 0.5 percent of the cement shot
up to 10 000 for the health checker so
believe me a person buying a policy of
50 lakhs
is getting at 10 000 Health checkup
every year and that Health checkup will
be provided through a cashless Network
so you just have to bring a number
toll-free number the I will ibr will
guide you to the RT they will give you
an option nearest option where the
health checkup can be availed according
to your policy plan and will fix your
appointment and the health checkup can
be done on cashless basis you don't have
to pay anything the package isn't are
designed by us
and that packages can be available any
kind of a payment
now the unique thing which this product
has like everybody uh or just uh before
the foundation was talking about the
worldwide cover
so what is unique about this worldwide
cover which is not available in the
market
I will say
this is the only worldwide cover which
is available in the market which doesn't
have any kind of resistance like
some company covers only like a limited
disease critical illness some company
cover only emergency cover so here in
Health Advantage Apex plus what you are
getting all kind of plant illness all
kind of unplanned illness is covered
without any kind of a restriction there
is only one thing so whenever we claim
for a worldwide there's a ten percent
copy
so now what happened I will tell you I
will give an example a person has
basically gone for a vacation and
certainly something happens to uh other
in short and his need of a emergency
hospitalization so we have a vendor in
our out of India which is a well where
we have toll-free number you can call
the vendor you can go to the hospital
and you can Avail cashless worldwide
coverage just believe me it's not a
reimbursement only we are also providing
cashless specialty abroad out of India
so you can claim your uh the cover as a
on cash based basis in case even if you
want to claim it on a reimbursement
basis that also is doable so you can
have your choice in case you are going
abroad you can do it cashless if you
want input on a reimbursement machine
will do that also only one thing the
length of State wherever you go in
abroad shouldn't be more than 45 days
because this cover is not for a foreign
National or a person deciding it out of
India but this cover is a for a person
who is basically studying in India but
going abroad maybe because of a business
trip or maybe because of a Leisure trade
that's the reason there's a cap of 45
days in a year the trip can be two times
so total cumulative days which we are
bringing is 90 days
and in case of a plant hospitalization
you just have to intimate us
we will give approval and you can go
abroad and you can do treatment so there
is no restriction on the treatment that
I will cover only this certain 18
illness or maybe nine illness so there
is no restriction it's your choice it's
your product an illness you can go
abroad and you can take the treatment
another most uh talkative point I think
pre and post where we got a lot of
feedback okay 30 60 60 90 is not a
basically a uh feature which are looking
we want 6180 so now that's the uh option
we are having 6180 so there is no choice
to the customer now 30 60 60 90 I think
that's create a confusion in the market
so we have inbuilt uh pre and post at
1680 days inner product
coming to air ambulance I think uh the
feature is very common in the market and
everybody is aware but the good thing is
that here also we don't have any
restriction so suppose in case if you
have gone for a vacation or
basically uh anywhere where we the
domestic ambulance is not reachable so
example you are on the hill you are
doing a tracking and a certain heart
attack
uh occurs to you and you don't have any
kind of domestic components to reach to
you so you can call and you can book air
ambulance where the ambulance will
basically uh pick up pick you from that
hill and make you available to the
nearest Treatment Center in whether in
that City or India nearby City to the
hospital so here we are not saying okay
basically the we will cover only to the
nearest hospital but to the nearest
hospital where the treatment can be
available so it's not okay
available
I think uh I mistake this slide have
been moved ahead no issue I think
yeah so another is Home Care treatment
so in home care wherever the treatment
can be available at home and the doctor
advice okay that treatment can be taken
at home like in Corona covered times uh
you have built this kind of facility at
in a product like Chi so here we have
inbuilt the product so any kind of
hospitalization uh where the doctor is
advised that can be taken at home like
forward Dengue or any kind of a gastro
problem where the treatment can be done
at home we are traveling that up to five
percent of the submission maximum to 25
000.
teleconsultation I think amitabhar
already talked about so yeah we don't
have any capping on on telecon
situations it's a unlimited telecon
situation so anytime during any
day any time of the day it's 24 7
available so even at the midnight two
o'clock in case you are looking for any
kind of consultation you can take you
can download or I take care app you can
just log in and you can just click the
button uh or teleconsultation and the
call will come to you and you can
basically get the treatment there and
there and also the prescription can be
mailed to you there and there so it's a
very online I will say it's a
hassle-free kind of a process where you
don't need any kind of a physical
involvement everything is been done
through I'll take care of
so I won't take much time on Adam cover
because everybody is aware about modern
dcipa claim protector where basically on
additional premium we pay the
non-payable also but one thing I will
just want to highlight about maternity
that
is only nine month waiting period in a
maternity plan
yes I think absolutely yes whatever you
heard is correct so we don't have a
wedding period of two years or three
years it's a nine months so once you've
opt for this plan you have to pay the
premium for three years and your modern
ticket will start right from
nine months one day and the good thing
the sublimit of maternity is 10 of the
submission maximum up to 10 lakhs
so believe me in case a person is buying
a policy of one CR he's getting a
mortality coverage of 10 lakhs
and the newborn baby cover twice of
maternity cover so in case we are in
modern degree of 10 lakhs the newborn
baby cover becomes 20 lakhs and that
cover is available till 90 days of the
uh baby born after that the person have
to enroll the baby into the normal
policy so isn't it the exciting feature
where your maternity also in a newborn
baby cover where you will see the most
of the hospitalization in most of the
delivery time happen the newborn baby
needs some kind of incubator or some
kind of a care uh generally the we have
seen a jaundice kind of claim is very
common to a newborn baby so that is also
covered up to twice the amount of
modernity
the last point which I want to highlight
here is Si protector
so as I politicize something where what
happens uh every year there is an
inflation
there is certain inflation or six to
seven percent where the value money
decreases but your sum in short remains
fixed
so when you opt for this feature what
happens your summon shot also increases
accordingly as per the inflation suppose
we have taken example of six percent the
current inflation rate is six percent so
every year your sum in short will
increase six percent irrespective of
claim foreign
vaccine discount we also want a customer
to be healthy and to take care of his
health
so what happens this is a vaccination
against the endless pneumonia
so any adult member who have already
taken this vaccination this is a
lifetime vaccination where customer has
to take this vaccine only once in a
lifetime and we will reduce your premium
by 1.5 percent every year so it's not
one time discount so we are using the
premium every year 1.5 percent because
we believe that this vaccination will
help the insured and even us in
basically uh keeping our health uh
healthy and also this will reduce uh the
person uh risk of falling uh ill due to
pneumonia
next slide please
so I think uh we've already discussed
about Day Care treatment where we have
removed the limit of 586 to already care
SI protector your summation will
increase according to the inflation rate
claim predictor so whatever the list of
non-table item will be become payable
once the customer opted is covered
another new thing which we have
introduced in other value added service
is ambulance assistance sometimes what
happens the customer is not available
to our customer also
next please
so to sum up I think the sum insert
option are from five to three so you
have various summation option of 10 15
20 25 30 40 and so on
there is no capping on a room rent so
that's a good thing I think so whatever
should you buy five leg and above you
have your choice you can uh go to the
hospital with no capping but again uh
it's a it's awesome in short so we
should choose it wisely and according to
some ensure this shows our room category
so that the summon shorts are sufficient
to cover your illness
we can have policy of one year two year
three year the plans available here are
seen as our product like Chi one added
one plus one one plus two two adult two
plus one side two plus two two plus
three
the product doesn't have any kind of a
copy but in case the customer want to
reduce the premium we have an option
where the customer can opt 10 and 20 of
the copay amount
so uh for example a person a 15 for a
twenty percent copy the premium will be
reduced accordingly and on any claim uh
20 of the claim will be won by the
insurer
so wellness program yes wellness program
is available in the product there are a
lot of activities which we have to do
like HRA are doing certain tests uh if
any person have joined gym uh or doing
Marathon so all this host of services
basically you can upload the document on
the I'll take care app and you will get
some points against that and every point
is equivalent to 30 percent and the good
thing about this Wellness is that once
your point is accumulated to a certain
amount you can get a person renewal
premium discount
so this five percent is not basically
you can enter investment as an opt but
the good thing here
that you will get a discount of Maximum
five percent every year so in case you
want to uh give get a discount of five
percent you maintain your health you do
all the activities and that's all in
renewable time of renewable you're
getting a five percent discount on it
remember because of your good habit good
behavior and the good uh physical
activities
period and specific exclusion we have
kept it simple two years so there is no
option of three years four years so it
is easy to understand to the customer to
our Channel partner so there's only one
waiting period of two years
and as already spoken about in case
anybody want the OPD coverage they can
opt for beefy Trader which is available
to all the sub insured options from five
to three under 300 lakhs so one can
choose beef with wherever they want to
Avail the OPD benefit
so I think the product is very
exhaustive very comprehensive and we
tried our best to cover accommodate all
the feedback which we got in last one
year and as we already said okay this is
not the end I think every three months
uh we are going to come with a new
product and whatever the feedback which
we are getting during this period
definitely will be accommodated in a new
product as we move forward
so that was all from the I think the red
side I think over to you in the Jeep to
take it ahead
foreign
those
yes sir thank you
uh thanks everyone for the investigation
um
very excited about the project product
Priyanka
foreign
or is it optional cover
s
[Music]
you are mute
granted community
foreign
so every claim free year you will get 20
additional and for every claim year you
won't get anything and maximum it can be
claimed uh basically earn is 100
essay protected
which is nothing to do with claims
so what we believe okay every year there
is certain inflation where the risk of
the coverage basically increases by six
percent so what we are doing here every
year irrespective of the claim we will
give additional some insure of six
percent yeah
every year as per the inflation rate we
decide currently it's around six percent
so both the features are different
granted cumulative bonus is part of a
basic summon shot and in case if you
want to Avail aside protector you have
to pay additional premium it's an
optional add-on cover
limits
uh so uh yes
to these modern treatments except for
bariatric surgery
the limit it is limited to fifty percent
of some insured maximum up to uh 10
lakhs
whichever is lesser uh coverage surgery
apart from that
um
surgeries and all modern treatments are
covered
um
and the best part of it is
foreign
[Applause]
we have changed it to 60 180 days so uh
can the customer uh go back to the
original one three thirty sixty UH 60 80
.
so you have to make it basically
convenient and easy to understand what
happens we have fixed the pre and post
limit so our pre-hospitalization period
is around 60 days and posted on quantity
days and uh this is not uh flexible now
so every person opting for any policy
any sub insured will get the same uh pre
and post limits
here 6180 will be fixed
no other option is available yes correct
um another one Abhishek uh I think I
already covered
uh is there any limit on
teleconsultation
so as I already said okay basically
consider is something basically we feel
any anyone can require n number of times
uh so that's the reason basically we
haven't kept any kind of capping on
teleconsultation and good thing about
that again I am repeating it's available
24 to 7. so there's no restriction on
teleconsideration so uh in short can
basically enjoy the service of telecon
solution at any time during uh anywhere
and uh the good thing I think you
realize during the covet period when
people didn't want to go to basically
hospital or a DC that's the reason
basically we opened this capping of uh
permitted previously it was around two
teleconstitution but now seeing the
response and seeing the demand we have
opened it uh to unlimited times
Eva this is amazing feature uh and to
have it unlimited times is just awesome
um so uh we'll just take one last
question now uh Priyanka uh is Home Care
treatment covered under this plan and uh
is there any restriction related to it
five percent of some insurance
this is obviously not for emergency
situations but essay situations
the treatment will be covered yeah
foreign
thank you
levels also to see all the queries that
you have or any concerns that you have
regarding our product our services is
taking care of Janice notifications
thank you so much team for joining uh it
has been a lovely event and looking
forward to a great success to this
product
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
foreign